{
    "subject": "Brian_Presley",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Erin_Hershey_Presley",
    "human_readable": "Brian Presley is married to Erin Hershey Presley.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9799813628196716,
            "question": "To whom is Erin Hershey Presley married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9774588942527771,
            "question": "Is Erin Hershey Presley married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.957566499710083,
            "question": "Is Erin Hershey Presley married to someone famous?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9573555588722229,
            "question": "Are Brian and Erin Hershey Presley a couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.939024031162262,
            "question": "Who is Brian Presley married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9249709844589233,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Brian Presley and Erin Hershey Presley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8517659306526184,
            "question": "Does Brian Presley have a spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8317829966545105,
            "question": "Who are Brian and Erin Presley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7513936161994934,
            "question": "What is the name of Brian Presley's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7227565050125122,
            "question": "What is the name of Brian Presley's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Brian Presley is married to Erin Hershey Presley.",
            "html": "yago_12093_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Brian Presley's wife?",
            "html": "yago_12093_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Brian and Erin Presley?",
            "html": "yago_12093_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Brian Presley have a spouse?",
            "html": "yago_12093_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12093_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12093_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12093_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12093_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12093_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12093_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12093_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12093_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12093_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12093_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that the triple \"Brian Presley is married to Erin Hershey Presley\" is indeed supported by the documents.\n\nHere's my response in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Brian Presley and Erin Hershey are married. For example, one of the documents states: \"Erin Hershey (Alison Barrington) and Brian Presley (Jack Ramsey) were married on July 27th in a ceremony in Santa Barbara at the Bacara Hotel.\" Therefore, the information supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}